Hello and welcome to a walk-through of taking my course, Python for Everybody on Udemy and doing an autograder exercise.
So you'll be cruising around through this course and you'll end up with facing the Python autograder that is built into Udemy.
So the assignment here is to write a program that uses a print function to say, "Hello, world."
And I give you some bad code. Now, this one's too easy, but I'm just going to say, "Run tests," and this is going to fail because it's got a mistake in it.
Print queue. And so the point is, is when you're writing a more complex one, this doesn't necessarily give you a bunch of output.
Let me go ahead and fix this and make it be print, "Hello, world," and then run the code.
And the code runs, and there it comes out with, "Hello, world," and then you can run the tests and you can pass.
Now, this one is simple enough. You're going to pass it. You're going to run the test, but sometimes you want a little better way to work with this stuff.
And so I've provided a couple of different ways to do this. If you can do it all in this autograder, ignore everything that I'm about to tell you.
So these autograders are also available in my autograder that I provide, and you don't need to log in for any of this.
And so you put your code in here and then you run it, and you can see the output, and then you run tests.
And it tests all the things, and it's a little simpler.
And so you can do this, and I will give you this URL because you need to know which exercise that is that you need to do in this particular thing.
Now, another thing you might want to do is simulate a little bit more like how a real software developer would do this.
And so this is like an integrated development environment. You can use an editor on your computer. You can install Python on your computer.
What I've done here is I've given you a very simple browser-based approximation to a file system, file system, an editor, and a little shell.
It's a Linux-like shell. It has help-ls to list files, rm to remove files, and you can run the Python.
And so it's got the text files that you're going to use in various assignments, and these things are already here.
OK. And so I can then type Python main.boops.
Well, let's make a mistake.
Python may.py.
No such file.
Python main.py. I kept messing up.
OK, so this is and this basically is more like the way you would do this if you were editing it locally on your computer in a shell or an IDE or whatever.
So I give this so you get used to the notion of how you iterate.
So if I make the change here, I can say print hello world.
And then I can and I can it saves automatically. Hit the up arrow. I run Python main.py and it runs.
Now, this doesn't have any autograder in it, but what's cool about it is you can make files, you can upload files, download files.
This does not use any server.
It doesn't talk to your local computer, but you can upload and download files into this little thing.
These are all stored locally in your browser.
And so this doesn't require and they're executed locally in your browser.
This doesn't require any server. You can do anything you want here.
You're really using your browser to develop Python. It's pretty amazing what they're doing.
I have other courses that will teach you how this is done.
But for now, we're just let's just be amazed.
OK, so this is the playground. This is kind of approximating what it's like to run locally.
So what I'm going to do is I'm going to show you how it would work if I was running locally with Python installed on my Macintosh.
So I'm first going to download this and it downloads this into the folder downloads.
And so I'm going to go keep this downloads folder up there. I just downloaded this Python program.
And so I can open a command line and I'm in my download folders and I can type the command ls.
Very similar to what we're doing over here, typing ls.
I can use an editor, use one that you probably won't want to use called main.py.
And there is that Hello World. And then I can say Python 3 main.py.
And it says Hello World. And so what I'm doing in the shell that you can use, it's free.
There's no login. I have no servers except to put up the text.
And so you can basically approximate. And if you were using Linux, you would use these exact same commands.
And so let's just go back. You can do all your work.
And if you can get things to figure out and run the code and run the tests and you like this and it works for you,
then ignore all my other alternative ways to do this and just do your do your assignments.
Get your credit and then move on to the next lecture from Python for everybody.
So thanks for watching. I hope this has been helpful. Cheers.